[
    {
        "question_number": 1,
        "correct_answer": "A\nI, II, III and IV",
        "question": "Question1"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 2,
        "correct_answer": "C\nIn a row of a relational table, an attribute can have more than one value",
        "question": "Question2"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 3,
        "correct_answer": "A\nA",
        "question": "Question3"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 4,
        "correct_answer": "A\n7",
        "question": "Question4"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 5,
        "correct_answer": "C\nHashing will outperform ordered indexing on Q1, but not on Q2",
        "question": "Question5"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 6,
        "correct_answer": "C\nIII only",
        "question": "Question6"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 7,
        "correct_answer": "D\nOnly I, III and IV",
        "question": "Question7"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 8,
        "correct_answer": "B\n3",
        "question": "Question8"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 9,
        "correct_answer": "A\n{M1, M2, M3, P1}",
        "question": "Question9"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 10,
        "correct_answer": "B\nCourses in which a proper subset of female students are enrolled.",
        "question": "Question10"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 11,
        "correct_answer": "C\nNames of employees with no immediate female subordinates.",
        "question": "Question11"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 12,
        "correct_answer": "A\nrelation r(R) is in the outer loop.",
        "question": "Question12"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 13,
        "correct_answer": "A\nA",
        "question": "Question13"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 14,
        "correct_answer": "D\nall of his/her dependents.",
        "question": "Question14"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 15,
        "correct_answer": "B\n3",
        "question": "Question15"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 16,
        "correct_answer": "B\nBD → CD",
        "question": "Question16"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 17,
        "correct_answer": "B\n2NF",
        "question": "Question17"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 18,
        "correct_answer": "null",
        "question": "Question18"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 19,
        "correct_answer": "C\n3",
        "question": "Question19"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 20,
        "correct_answer": "C\nMin 2 and max 3",
        "question": "Question20"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 21,
        "correct_answer": "B\nmn and 0",
        "question": "Question21"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 22,
        "correct_answer": "C\nc",
        "question": "Question22"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 23,
        "correct_answer": "D\nd",
        "question": "Question23"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 24,
        "correct_answer": "D\nd",
        "question": "Question24"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 25,
        "correct_answer": "null",
        "question": "Question25"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 26,
        "correct_answer": "A\n0",
        "question": "Question26"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 27,
        "correct_answer": "A\nEvery entity in E1 is associated with exactly one entity in E2.",
        "question": "Question27"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 28,
        "correct_answer": "C\nr LOJ (σB<5(s))",
        "question": "Question28"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 29,
        "correct_answer": "B\n(2)",
        "question": "Question29"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 30,
        "correct_answer": "A\nNames of sailors who have reserved all boats called Ganga",
        "question": "Question30"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 31,
        "correct_answer": "A\nin 1NF but not in 2NF",
        "question": "Question31"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 32,
        "correct_answer": "B\nDashed ellipse",
        "question": "Question32"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 33,
        "correct_answer": "C\n(A) and (B) are true; (C) false.",
        "question": "Question33"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 34,
        "correct_answer": "D\n3",
        "question": "Question34"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 35,
        "correct_answer": "B\nprimary key ⊆ candidate key ⊆ super key",
        "question": "Question35"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 36,
        "correct_answer": "B\npk(R1) → pk(R2)",
        "question": "Question36"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 37,
        "correct_answer": "B\nmn & 0",
        "question": "Question37"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 38,
        "correct_answer": "B\nBoth II and III",
        "question": "Question38"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 39,
        "correct_answer": "D\nAll of the above",
        "question": "Question39"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 40,
        "correct_answer": "C\nExam (ExamID, NID, ExamName)",
        "question": "Question40"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 41,
        "correct_answer": "B\nD1xD2x...xDn",
        "question": "Question41"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 42,
        "correct_answer": "A\nreducing the number of joins required to satisfy a query.",
        "question": "Question42"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 43,
        "correct_answer": "D\n(a), (b) and (c) are true.",
        "question": "Question43"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 44,
        "correct_answer": "A\nI only",
        "question": "Question44"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 45,
        "correct_answer": "B\nA small open diamond at the end of a line connecting two tables",
        "question": "Question45"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 46,
        "correct_answer": "B\nA ->B, A->>C",
        "question": "Question46"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 47,
        "correct_answer": "D\n3, 4, 1 respectively",
        "question": "Question47"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 48,
        "correct_answer": "D\nII, III and IV only",
        "question": "Question48"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 49,
        "correct_answer": "C\nII and III only",
        "question": "Question49"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 50,
        "correct_answer": "C\nII only",
        "question": "Question50"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 51,
        "correct_answer": "A\nTo allow duplicate tuples in the table by filling the primary key column(s) with NULL.",
        "question": "Question51"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 52,
        "correct_answer": "D\nABD",
        "question": "Question52"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 53,
        "correct_answer": "C\n(d)",
        "question": "Question53"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 54,
        "correct_answer": "C\nOwner Entity Set",
        "question": "Question54"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 55,
        "correct_answer": "B\nJoin",
        "question": "Question55"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 56,
        "correct_answer": "A\na cartesian product of two relations followed by a selection",
        "question": "Question56"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 57,
        "correct_answer": "B\nGRANT & REVOKE",
        "question": "Question57"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 58,
        "correct_answer": "D\nAdding suitable attributes",
        "question": "Question58"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 59,
        "correct_answer": "B\nAE",
        "question": "Question59"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 60,
        "correct_answer": "B\nLogical Data Independence",
        "question": "Question60"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 61,
        "correct_answer": "A\nInner Join",
        "question": "Question61"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 62,
        "correct_answer": "A\nPk(r1 ) → Pk(r 2)",
        "question": "Question62"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 63,
        "correct_answer": "A\nDiamonds with double/bold border",
        "question": "Question63"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 64,
        "correct_answer": "C\nThe sum of all employees' salaries",
        "question": "Question64"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 65,
        "correct_answer": "B\nIf Y is deleted, then X is also deleted",
        "question": "Question65"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 66,
        "correct_answer": "D\nOperations (d) and (a) will cause violation.",
        "question": "Question66"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 67,
        "correct_answer": "A\n(A)",
        "question": "Question67"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 68,
        "correct_answer": "B\nSubschema",
        "question": "Question68"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 69,
        "correct_answer": "A\nProject",
        "question": "Question69"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 70,
        "correct_answer": "C\n(a) and (c) happens",
        "question": "Question70"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 71,
        "correct_answer": "B\nTransitivity, Augmentation and Reflexivity",
        "question": "Question71"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 72,
        "correct_answer": "D\nTuples in a weak entity set are not partitioned according to their relationship with tuples in a strong entity set.",
        "question": "Question72"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 73,
        "correct_answer": "D\nNormal Forms",
        "question": "Question73"
    },
    {
        "question_number": 74,
        "correct_answer": "A\nA relation with only two attributes is always in BCNF.",
        "question": "Question74"
    }
]